anoox.com 2006-06-15

# AnooX Search Engine

Anoox knows your privacy is important. Our Privacy Policy explains what personal information we gather from you and what it is used for, as well as how it is protected. Of course this Policy does not govern other companies or websites we do not control.

In order to participate in, use and/or sign up for Anoox services you may need to complete a registration form or information gathering form to supply Anoox with certain information. We at Anoox are committed to protecting your privacy and enabling you to have a secure experience while visiting Anoox. Please read the following Privacy Policy below and contact us if you have any questions or concerns.

INFORMATION COLLECTED  
Anoox may collect certain information during the form filling or registration process such as personal identification information which may include your email address, first name, last name, address and nonpersonal information including your company, industry, website URL, age, gender, zip code, state, country, and operating system used. Anoox may also log certain information such as your IP address, browser type, and when you visited to help us improve our services. 

HOW INFORMATION IS USED  
Your information is used to operate and improve the service. You may also receive periodic announcements and communications about new developments at Anoox.

USE OF COOKIES  
We use cookies on Anoox in order to anonymously track our users preferences, to better serve our users and to improve Anoox. The cookies are not used to collect personal information from you and once you leave the Anoox website the cookie will terminate. Most browsers will accept cookies. Some Anoox features will not work properly without cookies, therefore you should have your cookies turned on.

ACCESS BY THIRD PARTIES  
Anoox will not share your information with third parties unless acting under a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to i)comply with legal requirements or legal process, ii)protect or defend the proprietary rights of Anoox or its affiliates, iii)enforce the Terms of Use, iv)act to protect the interests of others. Anoox will not rent or sell your information without first obtaining your permission. If the ownership of Anoox shall change, we will provide notice before your personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

SECURITY OF INFORMATION  
All personal information submitted to Anoox including but not limited to credit card and payment information is encrypted using SSL software. Off-line, only necessary employees who have a specific task are given access to user's personal information. 

CHANGE OF POLICY TERMS  
This Privacy Policy may change at any time. All changes will be added to this Privacy Policy accessible on this page. Any significant changes which may alter your rights will have a highlighted notice at the top of this page.

CONTACT US   
Any questions or concerns you may have should be directed to [contact us page](https://www.anoox.com/contact_us.jsp).
